<body>
	<post>
		<section>The Summathy Blog</section>
		This is a blog about mathematics. The site is currently under construction. For the time being it serves as a place to keep a short mathematical diary, recording whatever I though about and/or learned during the week. However I hope to expand the scope of this blog with videos and notes in the future.

		This website is built upon MathJax, XyJax and other javascript libraries. There may be problems with older browsers or those with javascript disabled.
	</post>
	<post>
		<section>Dayly Ramblings</section>
		<b>25.Aug.25</b><br/>
		There is a functor-homology description of $\Bbb{E}_n$-homology developed extensively by <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/0810.5147">Fresse</a>, <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1412.6032">Fresse-Ziegenhagen</a>, <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1412.6031">Ziegenhagen</a> and <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/0907.1283">Livernet-Richter</a>. It is based on a category $\mathsf{Epi}_n$, which should be related to the operator category of Batanin's pruned n-trees. Can we recover the (multi)complex defined by Livernet-Richter via the morphism of operator categories $\Bbb{O}^{\times n} \rightarrow \Bbb{O}^{\wr n}$?

		<b>26.Aug.25<b><br/>
		In <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/0909.5447">Fresse</a> it is shown that the dg-enhancement of the category $\mathsf{Epi}_n$ is Koszul. Explicitly this means the following: Considering dg-categories as monoid allows for a Bar-Cobar adjunction between dg-categories and dg-cocategories. Fresse uses this general framework to prove that an ad-hoc defined <i>Koszul-dual</i> dg-category of $\mathsf{Epi}_n$ is in fact a minimal model in the sense that it arises from a quasi-isomorphic sub-dg-cocategory of the Bar-construction. <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1102.3622">Livernet</a> shows a similar statement for a category of trees, which is used to define operads themselves. It is plausible that there is a general framework of Koszul-categories, which is closed under wreath products and the plus construction, streamlining the proofs of Fresse and Livernet...
	</post>
</body>
